evening
вечер
Good evening,
Вечер добрый
in my opinion, you already talked to you. You are a
по моему уже с вами беседовали Вы же
blogger, what kind of blogger am I on? I don’t remember you,
блогер какой я блогер на Я вас не помню
but what is your name?  In the
но я не в городе живу поселке
Orenburg region, you can
Оренбургской области можно поселок это
get a village, someone asked me for the
добыл кто-то у меня спросил к
Orenburg region, what is the name of the
Оренбургской области а как называется
village of the village Well,
поселок
why should I advertise it?
поселок Ну зачем мне это афишировать Я
]
[музыка]
What do you think, after the division of Russia, the
Как вы считаете после раздела России
Orenburg region should go to
Оренбургская область должна отойти
Kazakhstan or Bashkortostan Why do you
Казахстану или Башкортостан Почему
think that there will be some kind of division
считаете что какой-то раздел будет
because Russia will already fall apart there is
потому что Россия уже распадется есть
already international What are the
уже международное Какие предпосылки туда
prerequisites for the fact that Russia showed
предпосылки к тому что Россия показала
the whole world that it cannot protect
всему миру что она не может защитить
its territories, for example, Belgorod
свои территории например Белгородской
areas,
области
see if terrorist attacks
смотрите если террористические акты
occur on the territory of a certain area, do
происходят на территории какой-то
you think that this
области вы считаете что это
country is not capable of
страна не способна
America that collapsed How long did it last for how
Америка что распалась Сколько длился это
long
сколько по времени
for one day Well, how one day
на один день Ну как один день
is this terrorist And when you
вот этот террористический А когда вы
cannot return people to your city for a week
неделю не можете вернуть людей в свой
because  that they control it,
город потому что они контролируйте его
this is no longer a terrorist one. What example do
это уже не террористическая Какой пример
you give, well, in the city of Shebekino, you have a
вы приводите ну в городе Шебекино у вас
civil war going on there, yes
там гражданская война идет да
Civil
Гражданская
civil war when people are among themselves
гражданская война когда люди между собой
Citizens of the Russian Federation, the Russian
Граждане Российской Федерации русский
Corps and the Legion of Freedom of Russia are fighting
корпус и Легион Свобода России сражается
with other citizens of the Russian
с другими гражданами Российской
Federation,
Федерации
which has settled in the
которая засела в Кремле
Kremlin  region of the
вской области
Belgorod region between those who
Белгородской области между теми кем
are fighting between the Russian
проходят бои между русским
volunteer corps and the legion of
добровольческим корпусом и легионом
free Russia on the one hand, and it
свободной России с одной стороны и
was like who entered the
такое было это что такое кто зашел
Belgorod region who Wait
Белгородскую область кто Подождите на
this week This week This
этой неделе На этой неделе На этой
week
неделе
three days ago the Russian Volunteer
три дня назад русские Добровольский
corps of the Belgorod region took  captivity of
корпус Белгородской области взял в плен
Russian soldiers killed some,
российских солдат некоторых убил
even offered to the
предложил еще
governor of Belgorod to exchange
белгородскому губернатору обменять
you there is
вас там идет
a war between your civilian soldiers
война между вашими гражданского солдата
Who captured Why a civil war
Кто взял в плен Почему гражданская война
Because people with Russian passports
Потому что люди с российскими паспортами
who call themselves the Russian
которые называют себя русский
volunteer corps of
добровольческий корпус
the Belgorod region captured recaptured
Белгородской области захватили отбили
more precisely from the pounds of the Kremlin
точнее у фунты Кремлевской населенные
settlements new is Volzhanka  part of the city of
пункты новые это Волжанка часть города
Shebekino and captured Russian
Шебекино и взяли в плен российских
militants of the Kremlin
боевиков кремлевских
Border Guards And so on, they officially
Пограничников И так дальше официально
showed a video like that. The Belgorod
типа показывали видео Белгородский
governor refused to exchange these
губернатор отказался обменивать их этих
Border Guards, that is, he had
Пограничников то есть вел с ними
a discussion with them via the Internet,
дискуссию через интернет
we are talking about a civil war, a
мы с тобой говорим о гражданской войне
civil war is when citizens of a
гражданская война это когда граждане
state kill citizens of the same
государства убивают граждан этого же
states like this But if people come
государства так Но если вот люди заходят
from your side, it’s still a
с вашей стороны еще
civil war, this is when someone who
гражданская война это когда кто кем
is fighting with citizens of one country with citizens of
воюет граждане одной страны с гражданами
the same country True, that’s right, you
этой же страны Правда все верно ты
look at the Russian volunteer corps,
смотрите русский добровольческий корпус
this is Citizens of the Russian Federation, they have passports of the Russian Federation,
это Граждане Российской Федерации у них
that is,
паспорта Российской Федерации то есть
no, that is, you are
нет то есть ты
the Federation  I understand you,
Федерации я понял тебя
your border guards, this is also Citizens of the
пограничники ваши это тоже Граждане
Russian Federation
Российской Федерации
killing citizens of the Russian Federation
убивают граждан Российской Федерации
All sorts of ministers should fight there in the Civil War Why not,
министры там всякие Почему нет
that is,
то есть
it
есть
cannot be said
нельзя сказать что
that it is
что это воюет
citizens of Russia fighting against citizens of Russia
граждане России против граждан России
if some just there are five people five
если какая-то просто там пять людей пять
people And how many  people should
людей А сколько сколько людей должно
fight so that this is already considered a
воевать чтобы это уже считалось
Civil War,
Гражданской войны сколько
how many, well, you can imagine when
вот ну можно представить себе вот когда
the government is here,
вот правительство
if five people are
если пять человек
interested,
интересно
the number is not limited here
число здесь не ограничивается
when the government will have
когда правительстве будет
a misunderstanding when the government will
недопонимание когда правительство будет
fall apart Then there will be a
разваливаться Вот тогда будет
civil war This is an example where we were
гражданская война Это пример где мы были
on the verge of a Civil War this  in 90,
на грани Гражданской войны это в 90 года
90, when we were on the verge of a
90 года когда мы были на грани
civil war,
Гражданской войны
can you explain to me when
можете мне объяснить когда
in the eighteenth year, when there was a
в восемнадцатом году когда была
civil war in 1918
Гражданская война в 1918
Which ministers fought which ministers
Какие министры С какими министрами
Well, excuse me, there
воевали Ну тут уж извините здесь вообще
was this
было это
overthrow of power here in general Well, that is, it is possible without
свержение власти Ну то есть можно и без
ministers Come on Civil  of war, it’s true
министров Давай Гражданской войны правда
that here a new one was formed, a new one,
вот тут уже новая формировалась новая
as it were, a government There was no
как бы правительство Не было никакого
government
правительства
when citizens of one country,
когда граждане одной страны
moreover, you already
более того у вас уже на территории
had
Белгородской области была провозглашена
this Russian volunteer corps proclaimed on the territory of the Belgorod region
этим русским добровольческим корпусом
Belgorod
Белгород
enough to declare your country
достаточно чтобы объявить свою страну
Well, well, so that at least half of the village
Ну чтобы ну чтобы хотя половина селения
there dripped on  look at yourself And when
там накапало на себя смотрите А когда
we talk about the civil war, I’m
говорим про гражданскую войну я
not right. What half was the
правильно нельзя Какая половина была
essence such that in the Russian volunteer
суть такая что в русский добровольческий
corps Yes, I won
корпус Да отвоевал у кремлевских пункты
part of the Belgorod region from the Kremlin points and
часть Белгородской области и
proclaimed the Belgorod People’s Republic there a
провозгласил там Белгородскую народную
couple of days ago, maybe I don’t understand something
вот пару дней назад может я что-то не
a couple of days ago Now
пару дней назад Сейчас рассматривается
the candidacy of the head of the Belgorod People's
кандидатура главы Белгородской народной
Republic, Dmitry Karchinsky, is being considered. Here he is from
Республики Дмитрий карчинский Вот он с
childhood, he himself was not from Belgorod,
детства он сам родом не из Белгорода да
but his soul is for Belgorod since childhood, so he is
но душой за Белгород с детства вот он
planned
планируется
that he will be
что он будет
interesting to
интересно
read what kind of detachment how is it
читаете что за что за отряд как это
possible here is the Russian Volunteer Corps
можно вот русский Добровольский корпус
seized Belgorod seized
захватил Белгород захватил
power
власть
what  I couldn’t enter the village like that, my dad is busy,
что не мог так войти в село занято батя
now it’s happening there is Shebekino 400
вот сейчас происходит есть Шебекино 400
jellyfish pancake Again I got on the jellyfish of
медуза блин Опять попал на медузу
Freedom Let’s do something here
Свободы Давайте что-нибудь вот
Uzbekistan probably
Узбекистан наверное уже
should have sent a new war on
новую должен прислали война на
the territory of the representative said that they
территории представителя заявили что
completely control the Volzhanka, that is,
полностью контролирует волжанку то есть
some village was captured, I’m right
какой-то село захватили я правильно
I don’t understand They didn’t capture the
понимаю Не захватили отбили у
Russian
Кремлевской хунты русские
volunteers,
добровольческие
that is, they
то есть
captured it, that is, they occupied some, they took it, they recaptured
захватили Ну то есть заняли какие-то
Putin’s formation from the Kremlin Bank, the
формирование Путина
fighters who are so Well, what a small
бойцы которые так Ну и что маленькая
abandoned village Green point 5,000
заброшенный село Зеленый пункт 5000
people  Do
человек Сейчас
you think this is Civil
это вы считаете Гражданская
Seriously or something Did you read Yes that these
Серьёзно что ли Это вы прочитали Да что
are Russian fighters I
это бойцы российские
briefly read Russian Russian fighters
мельком прочитал бойцы русского русского
this is not a Russian Russian name This is
это не российский русский название Это я
how I understand the name of a Russian Russian
так понимаю название русского русского
we can call it as American there I’m
можем и назвать как американская там я
not so who is
не так кто
the entry corps
входитский корпус
Well some Slavs probably  it’s
Ну славяне какие-то наверное именно
Russian Citizens of the Russian Federation and
русский Граждане Российской Федерации а
where do they have their passports or what did they
где у них паспорта что ли
show in a video message they
они показывали они на видеообращении
made to Putin
делали Путину
Who heads the Russians Dobrovolsky
Кто возглавляет русские Добровольский
corps of
корпус
Moscow
Москвы
they freed from Wikipedia they are
они освободили от Википедии есть
from the Kremlin points Yes, the military formation is already
они от Кремлевской пункты Да уже
starting to liberate the territory of Russia,
начинает освобождать территории России
founded in August
воинское формирование основано в августе
22 by ultra-right Russian
22 года ультраправыми русскими
nationalists  fighting on the side of
националистами воюющими на стороне
Ukraine for
Украины так
14 years in the Ukrainian war, people from the
14 года украинскую войне выходцы из
Azov regiment and other units,
полка Азов и других подразделений
the views of the founder of the commander Denis
взгляды основателя командира Дениса
ultra-right, not the national RDK is subordinate to the
ультраправа не национальное РДК подчинен
Ministry of Defense of Ukraine,
Министерство обороны Украины
they originally entered, they already left
первоначально входил они уже вышли
initially Well, yes, originally they were
первоначально Ну да первоначально входил
part of the international legion of
в состав интернационального легиона
Ukraine from where the roots grow once again
Украины откуда корни растут еще раз
the roots of neither  where the
корни ни откуда
roots of the federation grow
корни растут Федерации
they were part of it
они были частью
would have shared his experience
получили бы его опыт
they are now not part of the face there
поделились они сейчас не с частью лицу
is an official statement of our
есть официальное заявление наших
ministers to that they have nothing
министров до что они не имеют никакого
to do with the armed forces of the cord
отношения к вооруженным силам укорда
where the roots grow from the Russian
откуда растут корни из Российской
Federation they are the same as the Russian Federation
Федерации Они же Российской Федерации
roots, for
вот прям три еще корни не корни так
example, yes, maybe Ukraine They are helped by
например да возможно Украина Им помогает
Ukrainian instructors Yes, I
инструктора украинские Да есть им
help them But this is your civil war,
помогаю Но это ваша гражданская война
these are citizens before our civil war,
это граждане до наше гражданская война
that is, Ukraine helps
то есть помогает Украина помогает
If Russia helped the Donbass militias there
Если Россия помогала там ополченцам
She also helped
Донбасса Она же помогала
where the roots grow in the Donbass
откуда корни растут на Донбассе
[music]
[музыка]
I sold you can  so to speak, yes,
я продавал можно так сказать поставляла
that is, it delivered to Ukrainian territory
да то есть на украинскую территорию она
somehow I guess
поставляла каким-то меня Я предполагаю
that Yes, where do the roots grow if Russia
что Да откуда корни растут если Россия
supplied me just now I just
поставляла мне сейчас только что
proved about one Yes, now I give you
доказывал про одну Да я теперь я тебе
advice, you brought it yourself,
совет ты вывел сам
it doesn’t matter
вот еще не важно
Russia supplied weapons to the Donbass
Россия поставляла оружие на Донбасс
it means where the roots grow from,
значит откуда корни растут
look where the roots of Russia can
смотри откуда корни России может быть
maybe protect their people it was not
может защитить своих народ это не был
your people it was the people of Ukraine you
ваш народ Это был народ Украины вы
recognized only in the twenty-second year
признали только в двадцать втором году
you recognized the DPR
вы признали ДНР
Putin forbids holding a referendum there in the
Путин запрещает провести референдум там
Putin region
путинской области
Why do you Look you recognized me well
Почему ваши Смотри ты признал мне хорошо
here I found  a man from Russia who
вот я нашёл человека из России который
admitted that the roots in Donetsk grow from
признал что корни в Донецке растут из
Russia Dasha Russia supplied weapons,
России Даша Россия поставляла оружие ты
well done, you gave me a very, very
молодец это ты мне дал очень-очень
good testimony.
хорошее свидетельство Супер Теперь
now we have a deputy
жителям Москвы вот сейчас у нас депутат
Explain to me if something
Объясни мне если э в Донецкой Народной
like this happened in the Donetsk People's Republic and what did they
Республике как-то так случилось да что э
send them e created a state for them,
прислали им э создали им государство
sort of like a pseudo state and sent leaders
вроде как псевдо и прислали руководители
from Moscow, where do the roots grow from?
из Москвы то откуда корни растут
Let me catch the idea again,
Еще раз давай чтобы я уловил мысль
see Russia supplied weapons
смотри Россия поставляла оружие
Russia
Россия
sent retired vacationers
присылала отставников отпускников
sent 1 leader of the so-called
прислала 1 руководителя так называемой
Donetsk People's Republic, a comrade,
Донецкой народной Республики товарища
wrestling with the question of
бородая вопрос
where the roots of Donetsk grow from,
откуда растут корни Донецкой
so Russian is not there People's
так Русский же там нет Народная
Republic from Russia, the roots grow, I
Республики из России корни растут я тебе
finally Russian you admitted you admitted
наконец-то русские ты признал ты признал
that Russia has been making conflict
что Россия с 14 года да делала конфликт
on  Donbass No, I didn’t admit that you
на Донбассе Нет я не признал что ты
said you
сказал
said that the roots grow from there you
ты сказал что корни растут оттуда ты
said that the roots grow from there, that is, the
сказал что корни растут оттуда то есть
roots of the conflict you said you said
корни конфликта ты сказал ты сказал
the roots grow from there everything No, that’s how you
корни растут оттуда всё Нет это ты так
said where
сказал откуда растут
you grow from Where do the roots grow
Ты откуда Откуда растут корни
from Russia
из России
the roots grow from Russia  Yes, and I turned to the
корни растут из России да и я обращался
Russian FSB Investigative Committee Yes, what
вследственный комитет России ФСБ Да что
kind of you should take your militants from here,
типа Вы должны забрать отсюда своих
they said that there is no
боевиков они говорили что нету никаких
evidence that the roots grow from
свидетельств о том что корни растут из
Russia. You are the first person who
России Вот ты первый человек который
confirmed that the roots grow from Russia.
подтвердил и что корни растут из России
I don’t care about this Russian video
я это видео русский мне уже не важно
what kind of people are there?
какой там народ главное что корень
thank you so much it’s
огромнейшее спасибо
unrealistic
нереально
subscribe us a kilogram right at a time
подпишись нами килограмм прям за раз
autumn and the ass is
осень а попок
more and more important YouTube driving
ц дуже и дуже важнева YouTube загоняя
us through the cardiorka into the shadow ban and
нас через кардиорке в теневый бан и
the hollow-boat video is not shown to people in
дужебоката видео не показывается людям в
private, information about
частном на показывается информация про
streams is shown in order to have a little
стримы тому для того чтобы мало
operational star squeak right at a time but
оперативный звездок пищица прям за раз а
try there in a kilo about cream video
попыт там в килограмме о Крим видео
information and we
информация и мы с вами
will show you
покажем вам
[music]
[музыка]